dilanustek@gmail.com

(778)903-0933

SUMMARY

I'm a customer-focused product manager with a passion for making products that people love. I drive product vision by leveraging my experience in computer science, user research and data analytics. Empowered with determination and purpose, my teams are able to deliver delightful products.

Work Experience

Associate Product Manager, Battlefy

Nov 2017 - May 2018

- Managed several features end-to-end from ideation to UX, development, QA, distribution, measuring KPIs, and performing retrospectives.
- Mitigated risk on several projects by conducting user interviews and analyzing user metrics to drive product data-informed decisions.
- Drove the vision and roadmap for a time-sensitive product affecting a highly visible segment of the user base with a reach of over 250,000+ page views per month. Shipped a real-time map veto system that received critical acclaim on social media and within the community.

Product Designer, Xtract.ai

May - Aug 2017

- Identified user needs and helped define product vision by interviewing potential users and customer journey mapping.
- Created user journey maps and low fidelity prototypes.
- Designed high fidelity mockups to achieve buy-in from stakeholders.

Research Assistant, UBC

May 2016 - Sep 2017

- Accepted to speak at Eurohaptics Conference based on my thesis *Designing zooming interactions for small displays with proximity sensors*.
- Crystallized product vision to Qualcomm and achieved buy-in from stakeholders to continue valuable research initiatives.
- Conducted user studies to define user needs and improve designs.

Software Developer, Monitise

Mar 2014 - Jun 2015

- Developed back-end of mobile apps for major banks.
- Developed web-based admin panels for Bayer, Boehringer, and Glaxo-Smith Kline.
- Used Java, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS.

Summer Technology Analyst, Goldman Sachs

Jun - Aug 2012 & 2013

- Increased traders' efficiency with a webapp allowing them to view social media trends to predict future activity.
- Increased workplace efficiency by developing an internal distribution-list tool.
- · Used Java, Twitter API, JavaScript, HTML, CSS.

EDUCATION

University of British Columbia

Specialization: Human-Computer Interaction

M.Sc. Computer Science

Aug 2017

Product BC

Product Management Mentorship Program

Apr - Aug 2017

Grinnell College

B.A. Computer Science Dec 2013

PATENTS

• Methods and Systems for Proximity-Driven Interactions, US Provisional Patent No. 62/481104

AWARDS

Microsoft Scholarship Recipient

2012 & 2013

• Winner of Goldman Sachs Technology Infrastructure Summer Intern Competition

2012 & 2013

TALKS

- How to Break Into Product Management Panel, Product Camp '18, Vancouver
- · Minimum Viable User Research, Product Camp '17, Vancouver
- Technical Opportunities Abroad, Google Women TechMakers '15, Istanbul, Turkey